vr.org 2011-10-11

# Privacy Policy - Host Virtual, Inc

    Host Virtual respects your privacy. When using our sites, you may get
    information, access online products and services, communicate with us or
    link to other Web sites with which we do business. While doing that, you
    may give us information so that we can provide enhanced products or
    services to you and to personalize your experience on our website. This
    online privacy policy describes how we use and protect Individual
    Identifying Information that you share with us. "Individual Identifying
    Information" is information that enables us to identify you, such as your
    email address, name, title and mailing address.
    
    This policy governs Web-sites owned and operated by Host Virtual. Our
    policy does not govern Web-sites of other parties to which we may provide
    links, because Host Virtual is not responsible, and can not control the
    privacy practices or content of those sites. To demonstrate our commitment
    to fair information practices, we have adopted leading communication
    industry privacy guidelines.
    
    We want to give you the comfort and confidence you need to fully
    participate in our online offerings so that we can better serve your needs.
    Therefore, here are the principles governing our information practices and
    other privacy aspects of our Web sites:
    
        * Information Collection and Use
        * Information Sharing and Disclosure
        * Host Virtual Customer Account Maintenance & Service Profile
        * Host Virtual Prospect Opt Out Profile
        * Security
        * Changes to this Privacy Policy
        * Questions or Suggestions
        * IP Information Collection and Use Practices
        * Cookies
        * Data Storage
        * Contact Us 
    
    Information Collection and Use
    
        * Host Virtual collects Individual Identifying Information when you
    register for a Host Virtual account, or use certain Host Virtual products
    or services, when you visit Host Virtual pages, and when you enter
    promotions or sweepstakes. Host Virtual may also receive Individual
    Identifying Information from our business partners.
        * When you register with Host Virtual, we ask for your name, email
    address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal
    interests, or other information. Once you register with Host Virtual and
    sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
        * Host Virtual also automatically receives and records information on
    our server logs from your browser including your IP address , Host Virtual
    cookie information and the page you requested.
        * Host Virtual uses information for three general purposes: to
    customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for
    certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new
    products.
        * Host Virtual routinely time-stamps and logs events (like features
    used, number of participants, length of meetings.) This data is used for
    accounting/billing purposes as well as for performance tuning and
    optimization of the Host Virtual services. 
    
    Information Sharing and Disclosure
    
        * Host Virtual will not sell or rent your Individual Identifying
    Information to anyone.
        * Host Virtual will send Individual Identifying Information about you
    to other companies or people when:
              o We have your consent to share the information;
              o We need to share your information to provide the product or
    service you have requested;
              o We need to send the information to companies who work on
    behalf of Host Virtual to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we
    tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the
    Individual Identifying Information we provide to them beyond what is
    necessary to assist us.);
              o We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
              o We find that your actions on our Web sites violate the Host
    Virtual Terms of Service , or any of our usage guidelines for specific
    products or services.
    
    Host Virtual Customer Account Maintenance & Service Profile
    
    You have the ability to edit your Host Virtual Account Information,
    including subscriptions for non-account specific email and general
    promotions, at any time. To request account maintenance, contact Host
    Virtual Customer Services at support@Host Virtual.com or call
    +1-866-229-3239 or +1-408-435-7088.
    
    Host Virtual Prospect Opt Out Profile
    
    Host Virtual gives you the ability to edit your prospect profile and
    preferences at any time, including whether you want Host Virtual to contact
    you about special offers and new products. If you would prefer not to
    receive messages from Host Virtual in the future, or if you just want to
    update your profile, please indicate your preferences through the following
    link. Host Virtual respects your privacy and will not sell or rent your
    personal information.
    
    Security
    
    Host Virtual Meetings take place within the context of a switched
    communications environment. With Host Virtual, any session information
    (such as applications, chat, polling data, documents, video, and voice)
    provided by participants within a meeting is never saved on the Host
    Virtual switching platform but is instead instantly switched between
    meeting participants. The Host Virtual switching environment is architected
    similarly to the telephone switching environment; once the call is over all
    remnants of the content of that call dissipate, leaving only a record that
    a call took place. Further, the only means to participate in a meeting is
    through the Host Virtual invitation and join process; Host Virtual
    employees can therefore only participate in Host Virtual customer meetings
    when expressly permitted by our customer.
    
        * Your Host Virtual Account Information is password-protected for your
    privacy and security.
        * In certain areas Host Virtual uses industry-standard SSL-encryption
    to protect data transmissions.
        * In other areas Host Virtual uses proprietary security methods to
    protect data transmissions.
    
    Changes to this Privacy Policy
    
    If we change any of our privacy policies or practices, we'll post those
    changes to this policy statement at least 30 days before they take effect.
    In limited cases, we may be required to disclose certain information to
    comply with a legal process, such as a court order, subpoena or search
    warrant.
    
    Questions or Suggestions
    
    If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback form on our
    contact us page.
    
    IP Information Collection and Use Practices
    
        * Host Virtual receives IP addresses from all users because this
    information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a
    Web page.
        * Your IP address is also stored in our user registration databases
    when you register with Host Virtual.
        * When a Host Virtual Web page is requested and viewed, that request
    is logged on our servers with information including the IP address of the
    computer that requested the page.
        * IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including to:
              o Diagnose service or technology problems reported by our users
    or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a
    specific Web company or ISP.
              o Send the most appropriate advertising based on geographic area
    or information derived from your IP address. Many IP addresses are commonly
    associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major
    corporations in specific regions or localities. Aggregate information
    derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.
              o Estimate the total number of users visiting Host Virtual from
    specific countries or regions of the world. 
    
    Cookies
    
    A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous
    unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a Web site's
    computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each Web site can send
    its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but
    (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access
    the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by
    other sites.
    
    Choices about Cookies
    
        * You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all
    cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so
    check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie
    preferences.)
        * If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Host Virtual
    products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be
    able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, many Host Virtual
    products and services do not require that you accept cookies.
    
    Host Virtual's Practices Regarding Cookies
    
    Host Virtual uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:
    
        * Access your information when you "sign in," so that we can provide
    you with customized content.
        * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Host
    Virtual's services.
        * Display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your
    interests and activity on Host Virtual.
        * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.
        * Conduct research to improve Host Virtual's content and services.
        * Require you to re-enter your Host Virtual password after a certain
    period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally
    accessing your account contents.
    
    Data Storage
    
    Account Information
    
        * When you register with Host Virtual or submit information to Host
    Virtual, a temporary copy of that information is routinely made to prevent
    accidental loss of your information through a computer malfunction or human
    error.
        * Host Virtual keeps your account information active in our user
    registration databases in order to provide immediate access to your
    personalization preferences each time you visit Host Virtual.
        * If you ask Host Virtual to delete your Host Virtual account, in most
    cases your account will be deactivated and then deleted from our user
    registration database in approximately 90 days. This delay is necessary to
    discourage users from engaging in fraudulent activity.
        * Please note that any information that we have copied may remain in
    back-up storage for some period of time after your deletion request. This
    may be the case even though no information about your account remains in
    our active user databases.
    
    Servers
    
        * The Host Virtual computers (called "servers") that send your Web
    pages and advertising banners process and store an enormous amount of
    information every day. These computer records are called "log files."
        * Log files are used for analysis, research, auditing, and other
    purposes, as described above. After this information has been used, it is
    stored and is inaccessible. Until the information is stored, your Host
    Virtual ID may remain in our active server log files.
    
    Contact Us
    
    If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of
    this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.
